Hello. I'm Callie and I teach [music]
natural everyday English. This is a
collection of videos from my spoken
English [music]
diary series. If you listen to this
video consistently, your listening
skills will improve and you'll [music]
get used to the way natural English
sounds in real life. It can also help
you build vocabulary, improve [music]
your speaking, and feel more comfortable
with essential [music] English
expressions. I recommend treating it
like a podcast and letting it play in
the background while [music] commuting
or before you go to bed. You can also
shadow and repeat the parts you want to
practice. If you keep coming back to
this video, [music]
English will start to feel more natural,
more familiar, and easier to understand.
I hope this helps you a lot. Let's get
started. Today is Sunday, so I'm going
to reflect on my week. I'm not going to
lie, I was feeling a bit homesick this
week. That rarely happens, but I think
it's because of the changing of the
seasons. I love fall time back in
Michigan. So, as the weather is getting
cooler here in Seoul, I'm thinking about
home a lot. I love Halloween.
I love going to pumpkin patches and
seeing the leaves changing colors. I
love watching football games. There are
many things that I love about fall back
at home. One thing I did that reminded
me of home this week was drinking a
pumpkin spice latte. Pumpkin spice
lattes are super popular in the US this
time of year. It doesn't seem to be a
very common drink here in Seoul, and
it's only seasonal in the US. So, it's a
bit hard to get, but Plant Cafe in
Itaewon offers one. So, I went there,
and it was so, so delicious. It's such a
cozy drink. It literally tastes like
fall. It's pumpkin, but there's a ton of
spices in it as well, like cinnamon or
nutmeg. So, for me, it's kind of like a
comfort drink. Even though I was missing
home a little bit more than usual this
week, luckily, I had a lot of things to
keep me busy and keep my mind off of
missing home. We filmed four videos this
week. I've been really busy with work,
but I'm feeling very energized and
passionate about my work lately because
I love the creativity of it, and I
filmed with some of my friends. It was
also lots of fun.
The one downside of working so much is
that I've kind of been neglecting my
health and my house. So, I've been
eating a lot of junk food. I've gotten a
lot of takeout and have been eating out
at restaurants.
So, I haven't been cooking healthy food
at home too much, unfortunately, and my
house was very messy. I know right now
it looks okay, but it's because I just
did a reset today. So, one of my goals
this week is to work a bit more on
work-life balance. Even though I'll
still be working hard, I want to try my
best to take care of my health as well.
I do have to give myself a little bit of
credit though. Even though I've been
very inconsistent with my workouts this
week, I did go for a lot of walks. I
love this kind of weather since it's
getting a little bit chilly outside. So,
I've spent a lot of time going for walks
in my neighborhood. Walking is one of my
favorite exercises because it's such a
calming activity. I put on my headphones
and I listen to music and just enjoy the
moment. These days, my playlist is
mostly Mumford & Sons. I actually went
to their concert here in Seoul a few
years ago and I'm such [music] a big fan
of their music. And it's perfect music
this time of year. I really recommend
checking them out if you don't already
know them. My high this week was going
to my best friend's birthday. Four of us
went out for dim sum. It was so
delicious. We ate at Din Tai Fung and
ordered way too much food. I think our
eyes were bigger than our stomachs.
After that, we grabbed a few drinks,
sang happy birthday, had a bit of cake,
and just spent some quality time
together. So, that was really nice. My
low this week was definitely my lack of
routines. Because I was busy with work,
I really didn't stick to my routines
this week. So, my sleep schedule was a
bit off. I stayed up late at night, and
then I slept in in the mornings, and I
hate doing that. I'm most productive in
the morning. So, when I sleep in, it
tends to stress me out. So, this
upcoming week, I really want to focus on
my routines. I want to go to bed early,
wake up early, eat healthy home-cooked
food, and be more consistent with my
workouts. That means doing yoga and
going to the gym two or three times this
week. I'm going to be real here and say
I'm already off to a bad start because
I'm filming this late at night. So, I'm
already failing one of my goals, but
I'll make up for it tomorrow. I hope you
all have a wonderful week and accomplish
all of the goals that you set for
yourself. Comment below what goals you
have this week. If this video was
helpful, please make sure to like it,
subscribe to our channel. Good night,
everybody. Sweet dreams. This week was
another busy, but very productive and
good week. I did lots of teaching, lots
of filming, lots of editing, and I even
made breakfast on live stream, which was
lots of fun. I filmed a video with one
of my friends, and we ate good food, and
talked about a really interesting topic.
I actually learned a lot while
interviewing her, but I don't want to
give any spoilers yet. I don't want to
ruin the surprise for you guys. Last
week I said that my goal was to exercise
more and to be honest, I haven't really
kept up with that. But I did do yoga a
few times and continued to go on my
walks and I did incorporate a little bit
of strength training into my morning
workout routine. I'm not really a big
gym rat and I think doing workouts at
home can be more comfortable and
convenient. So, even though I wasn't
perfect this week, it was still a little
bit of an improvement. Actually, for
yoga, I've been doing a yoga challenge.
It's a 90-day yoga challenge by Leslie
I found her videos on YouTube and they
are very helpful and they help me hold
myself accountable. I don't do it every
day, but I follow the schedule. I am now
on day 60 of 90. So, that feels like a
big accomplishment for me. Something
else that I'm very proud of myself for
this week is I feel like I've
successfully broken my TV addiction. I
really got into watching reality TV
shows. I feel like this habit started
during COVID because during COVID I
spent a lot more time at home. So, I
started watching a lot more TV, more
than I ever had in the past. And it just
developed into a really bad habit. I
found myself watching TV a lot
throughout the day while doing everyday
activities. If I was washing the dishes,
I also watched a show. While I was
folding laundry, I also watched a show.
And reality TV
isn't the greatest thing to watch
because although it's enjoyable, I don't
feel like I'm learning anything from it
or it's adding any value to my life. In
order to change that habit, I told
myself, "If I want to watch TV, I should
watch a Korean drama instead."
I feel like by watching K-dramas, at
least I'm practicing my Korean a bit.
I'm listening to Korean and it's a bit
more productive and it adds value to my
life. At least that's how I justify it.
Very proud of myself for that. I made
some progress on breaking that habit.
The K-drama I've been watching lately is
Hotel del Luna. I know it's a very old
drama, but I heard that it was very
popular and I'm really enjoying it. I
love the main character. She is very
strong and sassy.
I love lead female characters that have
a little bit of an attitude. Maybe it's
because
I can relate to them.
If you have any other K-drama
recommendations,
please let me know in the comments
because I'll be watching a lot more
K-dramas from here on out. When I have
free time and I'm not watching a
K-drama, I've been reading books, which
is pretty normal for me. I love to read
books. I am a bit of a bookworm. I
always have been. Even as a child, I
loved reading. I just finished this
book. It's called The Blind Assassin by
Margaret Atwood. Margaret Atwood is a
very famous author, and she's most
popular for The Handmaid's Tale. They
even made a show about that book now.
This is the second book I've read by
this author, and I really like her
stories, but they always take me such a
long time to read. That's because her
stories are always very complicated.
There are always multiple storylines
within one book. So, it's like reading a
story within a story within another
story. So, they can be a bit confusing,
but always towards the end of her books,
I get hooked, and I cannot put them
down. Even though this took me a long
time to finish, I did really enjoy it in
the end. I also attended some really fun
events this week.
I was invited to a skin care event by
Skin Chunsar. It was so nice because I
got to see their flagship store in
Myeongdong for the first time ever. We
had great food, we had champagne, and we
even learned how to make cocktails. They
had a professional bartender come in and
he taught us how to make three
cocktails. It was a lot of fun. And now
I'm thinking about changing my career
path. It was really great meeting other
creators and influencers.
I made a lot of new friends and just
made great memories with them. Finally,
I had another birthday party this week.
So many of my friends' birthdays are in
October. So this week it was my friend
Lorena from Spain. You must be very
familiar with her now.
It was Lorena's birthday. So to
celebrate her birthday, some friends and
I went to Pocheon to go glamping.
I have been to this glamping site so
many times now. It's my absolute
favorite. The tent actually floats on
water and you can fish right off of the
deck of your tent. It's just so
beautiful and peaceful and serene.
So, we drove to Pocheon and we
barbecued,
we ate cake, played games, did face
masks, watched a movie, and just had so
much fun together. So, overall, it was a
really great week and even though I was
busy, I was very productive and really
enjoyed myself. This upcoming week
should be a little bit more chill, I
think. I don't have as many commitments
this upcoming week. So, I think it will
be a good chance to focus on some of my
personal goals, like continuing to try
and exercise more regularly,
getting on a better sleep schedule,
practicing my Korean, these kinds of
things. I'm very excited for the week
ahead and hope that you all have a
wonderful week as well. These days, I'm
putting a lot of effort into making
useful content for you to practice your
speaking and improve your English
skills. So, make sure to subscribe to
our channel. Thank you for watching and
I will see you next time. Goodbye.
This past week was especially hectic
because it was my last week in Korea. I
thought I was prepared, but then it came
up so quickly and I had so much to do
before coming to the US. So, I was very
busy. My schedule was jam-packed. On top
of working, I also had to pack up
everything in our house and get
organized for moving day. My husband and
I have a storage unit in Seoul, so when
we come to the US, we pack everything in
boxes and take them to the storage unit.
>> [snorts]
>> I thought I didn't have many things in
our apartment, but when I was packing, I
realized how much we accumulated in such
a short span of time. So, packing it all
up was a little bit stressful. I also
had many errands to run, such as buying
souvenirs for my family, going to the
post office, and making plans for when
we're in the US. So, I had so much going
on. And our actual moving day was a
disaster. Things couldn't have gone
worse. We were already a bit behind with
our packing, and the weather was awful.
It was pouring rain, and we were
chaotically
running around our apartment trying to
finish everything very last minute. On
top of that, we had a train to catch at
6:00 p.m. because we had to go to
Changwon for my brother-in-law's
wedding. So, it was a bit of a time
crunch. When we were unpacking our boxes
and trying to put them into storage at
the storage unit, we accidentally
knocked over a plant.
So, my husband had to shovel up the dirt
and clean up in the pouring rain. I had
also ordered a new suitcase because my
husband and I didn't have enough
suitcases for our trip to the US.
And I realized when I was packing that
it was defective. Something was wrong
with the zipper and I paid a pretty
penny for it. So, I didn't want to keep
it if it was broken. So, on this already
busy, chaotic day, my husband needed to
go to a department store to try and buy
a new suitcase. Unfortunately, with the
rain and all of the traffic, we ran out
of time and couldn't buy a new suitcase.
So, in the end, we just used the
defective one.
With all of that going on, we were
extremely stressed out because it was
getting closer and closer to our
departure time. And we did end up
missing our train. It was a big
disappointment, but on the bright side,
there were available tickets for a bus
to Changwon not too much later. So, we
snagged those tickets and took a 4-hour
bus ride to Changwon. We arrived around
midnight and spent some time with my
in-laws before heading to bed because we
had a very early morning the next day.
The next day, we had to wake up bright
and early because it was my
brother-in-law's wedding. It was such an
exciting day and made me reminisce on my
own wedding. We saw so many of our
relatives and friends and all in all, it
was just a very beautiful day. My
brother-in-law looked very handsome and
the bride, of course, was stunning. I
couldn't be happier for them. I was also
very excited to wear my hanbok again.
The hanbok that I wore is very special
to me because it was a wedding gift from
my mother-in-law.
So, I enjoyed getting to wear it again.
We celebrated my brother-in-law's
wedding and ate good food with the
family. So, it was a great day, but
another very long night for us because
after the wedding, we took a bus all the
way from Changwon to Incheon Airport. It
was about 6 hours and we arrived very
late at night. We got some sleep and
went to the airport bright and early the
next day to catch our flight to the US.
It's a 13-hour flight, so it is very
long, but I can't complain too much.
There was not too much turbulence and I
just read my book and I watched two
movies during the flight. I watched
Twister and I watched a scary movie
called Longlegs. It's about a serial
killer, so it's a bit spooky, but I
enjoyed both movies. Now, I am in the US
at my dad's house, and I've already had
a great time catching up with my family.
I'm filming so much here and have so
much I want to share with you about my
time in the US. So, make sure to
subscribe to my channel and check out
the pinned comment below. I'll see you
all next time. Goodbye.
I'm finally back in Korea, so I wanted
to give you a little life update. It
feels a bit bitter sweet being back
because I had so much fun traveling in
the US. I went to New York for
Christmas, I went to Vegas, and I spent
so much quality time with my family in
my home state of Michigan. So, it was a
great trip and I made so many memories
there. But, I always miss certain things
from Korea when I'm in the US. So, it
also feels really great to be back. I
missed a lot of Korean food. I really
missed the fast delivery here and how
convenient everything is in Korea. And
actually, one of the things that I
always miss the most when I visit the US
is how walkable Korea is. I love the
wide sidewalks in Seoul and how I can
easily go for long walks here. In the
US, that always seems impossible. So,
it's been really nice getting to enjoy
all of the things that I've missed. As
you probably saw from a lot of my videos
that we filmed in the US, I did not eat
very healthy there. I ate a lot of fast
food and a lot of junk food. So, I'm
finally trying to get back on track with
my diet. I'm trying to practice more
healthy habits in order to jump start
these healthy habits, I started a
challenge called 75 Hard. It's a super
viral health challenge in the US these
days. This challenge lasts for 75 days
and you're not allowed to have any cheat
days. So, it's really tough. During 75
Hard, you have to follow a diet, work
out twice a day, drink a ton of water,
and read non-fiction books. And you
cannot drink alcohol. I'm filming a vlog
about my experience doing 75 Hard, so
make sure to check that one out. What
I've been struggling with the most
during the 75 Hard challenge has been my
diet. I set super strict rules for my
diet. For 75 days, I cannot eat any
takeout food or delivery food, and I
can't eat out at restaurants. So, every
meal must be cooked at home. I'm also
not eating gluten or sugar. So, my diet
is quite restricted these days. I enjoy
cooking, but having to cook every single
meal has been pretty exhausting. I
really miss Coupang Eats, especially on
days where I'm a little bit busier.
Tonight, I made beef stew. I also make a
lot of salads like chicken salad. I eat
eggs almost every morning for breakfast.
And now that the weather is getting
hotter, I'll start making my favorite
smoothie bowls for breakfast soon.
That's a staple for me in the summer.
I've also had a lot of fun catching up
with friends and family since I've been
back in Korea. I finally could go to a
book club meeting. I missed so many
meetings when I was in the US and it
made me really sad. I had a little bit
of FOMO. So, I was really happy to come
back and attend a meeting. We went to
the Han River for a picnic and we
discussed our book of the month, which
was Nonviolent Communication by Marshall
Rosenberg. To be completely honest, this
wasn't my favorite book.
I learned some new things while reading
it, but it wasn't my cup of tea. I
usually prefer novels or fiction books
over nonfiction books. But, we had a
really great discussion about the book
and I enjoyed it still. One book I've
read recently that I do really
recommend, surprisingly, is a nonfiction
book. It's called Quiet by Susan Cain
and it's about the power of introverts.
I could really relate to this book
because I'm actually an introvert. Many
people assume that I'm an extrovert, but
my MBTI is INFP.
So, when I was reading this book, I
really felt connected to it and I found
it very interesting because a lot of
people view being introverted as a
weakness, but she says the opposite,
that it's a strength. So, I really
recommend this book for anybody, but
especially if you're an introvert.
Recently, one of my subscribers
recommended the K-drama When Life Gives
You Tangerines, and I just started
watching it. I think I'm on episode 6 or
7 now, so I still have a long ways to
go, but I'm loving it so far. It is such
a heartwarming K-drama, but it's a real
tearjerker.
I think I need to watch it with a box of
tissues.
When I watch this show, I think what I
feel the most is respect for the older
generation. I became a really big fan of
IU as an actress. I first saw her in
Hotel del Luna, and then I watched Na Ae
Ajusshi, and now this new drama. So, I'm
a huge fan of IU. I think she's an
incredible actress.
My goal this week is just to stay strong
with my 75 Hard Challenge. I've been
really struggling with it lately, and I
cannot wait for it to be finished. I've
been craving bread like crazy.
I just want a sandwich or any kind of
carb, like a big bowl of noodles. I
think when the challenge is finished, my
first meal will be a big bowl of sujebi.
I love sujebi, and it just sounds
amazing right now. But, until then, I I
to stay strong, keep eating healthy,
keep going for my walks, drinking my
water, and sticking to my health
routine. Now that I'm back in Korea, if
you guys have any suggestions or any
type of vlog that you want to see while
I'm here, please let me know in the
comments below. And also, make sure to
check out the pinned comment. I hope you
all have a wonderful week and I will see
you next time. Goodbye.
The past couple of weeks have been a
little bit rough because I've been
dealing with some eye issues. First, I
got a stye in my right eye and then I
woke up one morning and my left eye was
in so much pain. I could barely open it.
I went to the doctor and they told me I
had pink eye. They gave me lots of
medications,
eye drops, and ointments. It's been
helping, but it's a slow healing
process. My eyes are still very
irritated and bloodshot. Since pink eye
is very contagious, I had to cancel all
of my plans, which was kind of a bummer.
So, I've been a big homebody lately. I
binge-watched a Netflix series called
The Resident. I really enjoyed this one.
It's a murder mystery and the main
character, a detective, is very quirky
and super smart. I thought the story was
really fun and interesting and it
definitely keeps you guessing. If you
liked Sherlock, you'll probably love
this one, too. Because I've been stuck
at home by myself all week, I've been
feeling a little bit lonely. So, I
talked to my family on the phone a lot
this week.
I even got to FaceTime with my baby
nephew. He's so cute, and listening to
him giggle and squeal really cheered me
up. I can't wait to meet him in person
one day. Since I've been feeling kind of
down, I decided to treat myself to some
fancy smoothies from a place called
Troubles. Their smoothies are kind of
like the ones from Erewhon, which is a
super fancy and expensive grocery store
in LA. The last time I was in LA, I
actually went to Erewhon and tried their
viral Hailey Bieber smoothie. It was
delicious, but it cost around $20,
which is outrageous. The ones from
Troubles here in Seoul cost around $7
each, so they're much more affordable.
I got the iceberg smoothie and the
strawberry smoothie. Both were really
good, but the iceberg smoothie was my
favorite. I highly recommend it and
think it's the perfect summer treat.
This week, I didn't do anything too
intense for exercise, but I've been
walking a lot on my walking pad. I
always try to get around 10,000 steps a
day and my walking pad really helps me
hit that goal. I usually walk while
working on my laptop. It's an easy way
to get some steps in and stay active
throughout the day.
I've been resting a lot and just taking
it easy so that I can get better and
start filming more videos soon. I always
have so much fun filming and I've been
brainstorming
new content ideas like crazy. So, I hope
you're looking forward to some new and
exciting videos coming your way. Stay
tuned and have a great week.
Goodbye. It's been a very busy couple of
weeks because
drum roll
we are moving to Busan. I'm very excited
because we'll be closer to family there
because my in-laws live in Changwon.
Also, I grew up in a beach town and I
love the water. Being by the water
always makes me feel so happy and calm
and I love swimming. So, I can't wait to
live next to a beach. We've been
decluttering our house and trying to get
rid of a lot of things that we don't use
anymore. We've been selling stuff on
Danggan and trying to live a more
minimalist lifestyle because we move and
travel so much, it's really stressful
having so much stuff. So, we're trying
to get rid of as much as possible and
only keep the essentials. Before leaving
Seoul, I also squeezed in one last trip
to my hair salon. I've been going to the
same hair salon for quite a while now,
so I'm going to miss it a lot. We didn't
do too much to my hair, but we touched
up the roots, trimmed the ends a little
bit, and put in some toner. It's a bit
darker than it was before, but in the
sun, it brightens up a lot. It always
feels nice getting a fresh haircut. I've
also been trying to meet up with some
friends to say goodbye before moving. A
few nights ago, I met up with a group of
friends and had dinner at a place called
Gokio. It was my first time ever trying
the Korean style rotisserie chicken and
scorched rice. I really recommend this
restaurant because not only was the food
delicious, but I also really liked the
atmosphere there. I think it's normally
an open-air restaurant, but when we were
there, it was too hot outside, so they
closed everything off and had the AC on.
Speaking of the heat, it's been so
brutal in Seoul these days. This
heatwave is no joke. I've been staying
inside a lot and blasting my AC. So, be
safe, everybody. Keep cool and stay
hydrated. Since I've been spending a lot
more time inside, I've been on a bit of
a movie kick. I recently went to the
movies on a double date with our friends
to see F1. It was really good and I love
going to the movie theater. It was a
feel-good movie. It was definitely
inspirational and Brad Pitt did an
amazing job, of course. One of my
favorite movies that I've watched
recently is called Companion. It's a
dark thriller about AI and there are so
many twists and turns. I was on the edge
of my seat the whole time. I was
screaming at the TV. It's really good
and I highly recommend it. If you've
ever seen the series Black Mirror, it
kind of has a similar vibe to that.
That's my favorite genre because it's
quite deep and it makes me think about a
lot of different things. While I've been
cleaning and packing, I've also been
listening to a lot of music. One song
that I have on repeat these days is
Golden from the movie K-Pop Demon
Hunters. It's so catchy. I liked that
movie, but I especially love the
soundtrack. I've also been listening to
a lot of Justin Bieber because he just
dropped a new album. I've been listening
to the song Go Baby non-stop and it
always gets stuck in my head. Life has
been a little bit chaotic these days
because of the move, so I haven't done a
great job at sticking to my routines,
but I still try to do yoga in the
mornings. I've been practicing Ashtanga
yoga and it makes me feel amazing. I've
definitely seen some improvements in my
strength and flexibility. I've mentioned
her before, but I always follow Leslie
Fight Master's yoga videos on YouTube.
Once we move to Busan, I can't wait to
switch it up and go for runs on the
beach. I want to enjoy the view while
getting my workout in. Anyway, that's my
little life update for now. I'm excited
to go to Busan, but I'm also feeling a
little nostalgic saying goodbye to
Seoul. Thanks so much for watching and
I'll see you next time. Bye. I'm about
to go to bed, but I wanted to give you
guys a little life update. I feel like
I've really settled in and adjusted to
life in Busan. I really like the vibe
here and there's always so many things
to do here on weekends. For example,
last weekend they shut down Gwangan
Bridge and lots of people were walking
on the bridge and eating brunch, which
was a really cool experience. Also, I've
been staying pretty busy because I
recently started taking Korean classes
again. To be honest, my Korean is a bit
rusty, so it's been really nice getting
back into a classroom and practicing my
Korean again. I take these classes twice
a week and they are actually provided by
the government. I'm kind of a nerd and I
love anything academic, so it's been a
lot of fun for me hitting the books
again and getting to meet new friends
here in Busan. The class is 4 hours
long, so I always get hungry and it's
not always easy, but the teacher is so
sweet. So, even though it's a very long
class, it's very enjoyable. I also
recently went back to Seoul because I
had a lot of events and meetings that I
had to participate in. Even though I
lived in Seoul for a long time, it kind
of felt like vacation. We rode the KTX
there and we stayed in a hotel in
Hongdae. So, I really felt like a
tourist. I was so shocked going out and
about in Hongdae because the lines at
Olive Young, in Daiso, and even the
pharmacy were insane. All of the lines
were out the door. It wasn't a super
long trip, but of course, I had to catch
up with some friends while I was there.
I met up with a friend for shopping in
Hongdae and we also enjoyed a really
delicious meal at a Chinese restaurant
there. The food was really delicious,
especially the Jajangmyeon. I really
recommend this restaurant, so I'll make
sure to share that info with you here. I
also met up with another friend for more
shopping in Seongsu and man, it was
packed there. I'm not usually a big
shopper, but I had a few things that I
needed, so I went on a shopping spree.
Everything in Seongsu feels so trendy
and hip and there were crowds of so many
young people there. It was a lot of fun
and I bought a purse that I'm obsessed
with. I was quite busy during this trip
to Seoul, but of course, I had to make
time to eat at some good machips while I
was there. I have two places that I
really want to recommend. The first one
is Travel Maker's. It's an American
breakfast spot and you can get a huge
breakfast with eggs, bacon, sausage, and
pancakes for a pretty affordable price.
The atmosphere of the restaurant also
really reminded me of home and the best
part is you get free refills for your
coffee. The other place I want to
recommend is more of a dessert spot.
It's called Acai Monkey. They sell Acai
bowls with all kinds of delicious
toppings like fresh fruit and granola.
And the owner there was so sweet and she
actually lived in Australia, which is
where she learned about this dessert and
decided to bring it to Korea. It's a
must eat while in Hongdae. One of the
biggest reasons why I went back to Seoul
was to film a video with Lee Seung Jun.
I was so excited and couldn't believe
that he reached out to me and invited me
to be on his show. Filming with him was
such a cool experience. He's really
down-to-earth and chill, so I felt very
comfortable filming with him. I will say
it was a bit challenging as well though
because everything was done on the spot.
He asked a lot of questions and I just
hope that I answered them all well. He
told me that he's learning English
because his goal is to do stand-up
comedy in the US one day, which I think
is really cool and I would love to see
him at a show there. I got my hair and
makeup professionally done, which was
also a really great feeling because I
rarely ever get glammed up like that. We
went to a photo studio so that I could
get some more profile photos. Finally, I
had an orientation for both our new
offline and online classes, as well as a
farewell party for the first boot camp
that just ended. I was really proud of
everyone's hard work and can't wait to
see what these new students can
accomplish. Now, I'm back in Busan and
just kind of getting back into my daily
life here, which I'm very excited about.
I hope you're all doing well and are
happy and healthy. Chuseok is right
around the corner, so I hope whether you
have plans or not, you enjoy yourselves
and have a safe and very happy holiday.
Take care and I'll see you next time.
Bye. I just got back from a solo trip to
Jeju. I went to visit a family that I've
gotten to know over the years and am
very close with. I hadn't seen them for
a really long time, so I wanted to spend
some good quality time together. I
packed a bag and hopped on a plane
Friday afternoon. When I arrived, the
mom picked me up at the airport and gave
me a little tour around the island. When
school got out, we picked up their two
daughters and went to one of their
favorite restaurants. It was an Italian
restaurant and oh my gosh, the food was
so good. We caught up over a bottle of
wine and lots of delicious food like
pasta, steak, and salad. I can't even
pick a favorite dish because everything
was incredible. It's in Hapjeong, so we
also got a beautiful view of the beach,
which was a nice treat. Afterwards, we
headed home and the girls and I made a
Halloween-themed
gingerbread house. Making gingerbread
houses together during the holidays is
kind of our tradition now. We each made
our own and had family and friends vote
for the winner. The oldest daughter won,
but they both did such a great job. Me,
on the other hand, not so much. But, we
laughed a lot and had an amazing time,
and that's what matters most. After all
of the excitement, I slept like a baby.
So, I slept in on Saturday and had kind
of a slow morning, which was really
nice. They made a reservation for us to
go on a yacht tour. So, that was our
first outing of the day. I love being on
the water, so I was super excited for
this part of the trip. The boat was
huge, and they had all you can drink
wine and beer, plus some snacks. We did
have two small cups of beer, but we
didn't go too crazy.
The weather was sunny and nice, but it
was extremely windy. So, there were huge
waves, and you had to be very careful
walking on the boat. Also, my hair was
blowing all over the place, so I looked
a little bit crazy. We all cracked up at
our photos because it looked like I had
a mop on my head. My pants were blowing
up like a parachute, too. I was just a
hot mess. We rode past a bunch of cliffs
and caves, and I really felt the island
vibe of Jeju there. We even got to go
fishing at one point. Unfortunately, we
didn't catch any fish, but some other
people on the boat did. Honestly, this
was probably my highlight of the whole
trip because we took so many photos
together and shared a lot of laughs. The
younger sister is super into horses
these days, so I promised her I'd go
horseback riding with her. I am
extremely inexperienced, and I was a bit
nervous, but it ended up being a really
cool experience. The staff took great
care of me and explained everything
really well. It also helped that I rode
a very old, slow, and calm horse. They
even called him Grandpa Horse. I think
he was the perfect fit for me. We spent
most of the time doing laps inside, but
at the very end, we got to go outside
for a little trail walk together. It was
really nice getting some fresh air and
enjoying the scenery. They also had a
really cute golden retriever there, so
we played with him and fed him lots of
treats. I really want a dog these days,
so take notes, cameraman. You can't
leave Jeju without having some black
pork barbecue. So, that's what we had
for our last dinner together. Fun fact,
the first barbecue I ever had in Korea
was black pork in Jeju. So, it was
really nice getting to enjoy that taste
again. The restaurant was really fancy
and looked like an art gallery. They did
all of the grilling for us and I ate so
much moksal. It's my absolute favorite.
It was the perfect way to end my trip in
Jeju and early Saturday morning, I took
a flight back to Busan. Time really flew
by, but this weekend was full of so many
precious moments that I'll never forget.
This week, I'm back to the grind with
work and school, but I'm feeling
refreshed and energized after a healing
weekend in Jeju. So, bring it on. I hope
you have a great week ahead and I will
see you next time. Good night. Can you
believe it's already almost 2026?
This year flew by. Since it's almost New
Year's, instead of reflecting on my week
like I normally do, this time I'm going
to reflect on my year.
A lot happened this year. It was full of
ups and downs, but I have so much to be
grateful for. So, I'm going to start by
reflecting on the highlights or most
memorable moments from my year. First of
all, I became an aunt for the first time
in February. My sister had an adorable
baby boy named Wes. Since I live in
Korea, I haven't gotten to meet him in
person yet, but we video chat as much as
possible and I already love him so much.
Another big life event this year was
moving to Busan. I lived in Seoul for
the past 10 years. So this was a big
change for me, but it's been a really
positive experience. Of course, I'll
always love Seoul, but Busan is really
starting to feel like home and living by
the beach has been amazing. Thanks to
you, some of my biggest accomplishments
this year came from my YouTube channel.
Our community reached 350,000
people. I received a best creator award.
And I just published my first book,
which honestly still feels like a dream.
I never ever thought I'd have the
opportunity to do that, so I'm extremely
grateful to you for making it possible.
It's also been a lot of fun getting to
meet some of you in person at events or
even when I'm out and about filming. I
always get so excited when I meet you,
so please, if you ever see me out and
about, come say hi. Of course, this year
wasn't perfect and I didn't meet many of
the goals that I set for myself. First
of all, I failed to reach my book goal
again. Every year I tell myself I'm
going to read 50 books and every year I
fail. I love reading and see it as a
form of self-care, which is why I try to
prioritize it. But, next year, I need to
be a little bit more realistic and set
my goal at 30 or something like that.
Another frustrating part of this year is
that I didn't take care of my health as
much as I wanted to. Health is really
important to me, but my workouts this
year were inconsistent and I ordered
delivery food way more than I'd like to
admit. Finally, at the beginning of the
year, I told myself I wanted to become
more financially responsible. Setting a
budget, paying off loans, and learning
about investing. But, honestly, it felt
overwhelming. So, instead of facing it,
I kind of avoided thinking about it.
That brings me what this year has taught
me. One big life lesson I learned this
year was to do it scared. I struggle
with self-doubt a lot. I had some really
exciting opportunities this year, but
sometimes I felt like I didn't deserve
them or wondered if I was good enough.
But, I realized that so many people feel
this way, so it's important to push
through the fear and the negative
self-talk. Do it scared. Another lesson
I learned is that nothing is ever
perfect and waiting for perfect usually
just means waiting forever. I'm a bit of
a perfectionist and hold myself to a
really high standard, so I often feel
like whatever I do has to be flawless.
But, of course, that's impossible. So,
instead of telling myself that I need to
be perfect, I'm trying to remind myself
that I want to be human. Everyone makes
mistakes. So, it's important to be kind
and patient with yourself and learn from
those mistakes rather than stressing out
or getting anxious trying to avoid them.
So, going into the new year, my
resolutions are actually pretty simple.
First of all, I really want to be able
to do a pull-up, just one. I know it
might sound silly, but I just want to be
strong and honestly, it just looks
really cool. It's kind of a flex. My
second resolution is to be more
consistent with my Korean studies. I
tend to do things in spurts. So, I'll
study extremely hard for a month or two
straight and then slowly, I stop. It's
very all or nothing, but I know that
when it comes to learning a language,
consistency is key. Studying even five
or 10 minutes every day is better than
nothing at all. So, next year, I'm going
to try really hard to make it a daily
habit. Finally, I want to have more
meet-ups with you guys. I'll probably be
heading back to the US sometime next
year. So, before I go, I want to meet as
many of you as possible and just spend
some good quality time together. I think
it would be a lot of fun. If I can make
it happen, I'll keep you posted on the
details. What are your New Year's
resolutions? Let me know in the comments
below. I hope you reach all of your
goals and that 2026 is the best year yet
for you. Happy New Year.
Can you believe it's already March? That
means the first quarter of 2026
is basically already done. Time is
seriously flying by. So, today I thought
it would be a good time to do a little
life update and talk about how 2026 has
been going so far. Lately, I've been
really focused on my New Year's
resolutions. Especially when it comes to
my health and fitness. Health is
something that's very important to me,
but last year I wasn't as consistent as
I wanted to be. So, this year I decided
to take it a little more seriously.
Recently, I started counting calories
and tracking my macros for the first
time ever in my life. It's not to diet
or restrict myself, but to make sure I'm
eating balanced meals and getting enough
protein. It's actually been really
interesting because it makes me more
aware of what I'm eating and how it
affects my energy. I've also been going
to the gym regularly and have become a
bit of a gym rat. I want to build
muscle, so I've been focusing more on
strength training. One of my resolutions
this year is to be able to do a pull-up.
Just one. I'm definitely not there yet,
but I'm working on it. One step I took
to help me reach that goal was buying a
pull-up bar for my house so that I can
practice more regularly. I'm also taking
yoga and Pilates classes, which I've
been really enjoying. It just feels good
to move my body more and prioritize my
health. Another one of my resolutions
this year was to do more meet-ups with
you guys. I don't know if this
technically counts, but I did a book
talk at Kyobo, which was a really
special experience. When I meet you guys
in person and hear your stories, it
really inspires me and motivates me to
keep going and to always try my best. I
also miss teaching offline sometimes, so
getting to meet you face-to-face felt
really meaningful. So, a big thank you
to everyone who came to the event. I
really appreciate it and I hope to see
you again soon.
Another great memory so far this year
was traveling to Vietnam. It was my
first international trip of 2026,
and it was a great one. First, I visited
Hanoi to see an old friend, and then I
spent time in Phu Quoc with my family.
The two places had completely different
vibes. Hanoi felt very fast-paced and
energetic, while Phu Quoc felt slower
and much more relaxing. It was so nice
catching up with my friend in Hanoi, and
I loved getting to spend some good
quality time with my family in Phu Quoc.
We made so many great memories together,
and now we have a lot of inside jokes
from the trip, so it was really great
bonding time. I love Vietnamese coffee,
and I tried so many different kinds when
I was there. I tried egg coffee, coconut
coffee, and even yogurt coffee, but my
all-time favorite was salt coffee. I
miss it so much. One random thing that
I've become completely obsessed with
lately is puzzles. I've been doing a lot
of Sudoku, and I also recently bought a
book called Myrtle, which is pretty
popular in the US. It's basically a
murder mystery puzzle, where you have to
figure out who committed the crime,
where they did it, and what weapon they
used. It actually reminds me a lot of
the board game Clue. It's so much fun.
By far, one of the worst parts of 2026
so far was getting food poisoning. I'm
not exactly sure what caused it, but I
think it might have been from salmon,
which is a big bummer, because I
actually really like salmon, but now I
feel very paranoid eating it. I threw up
so much and felt so sick that I even had
to get an IV at the hospital. On the
bright side, while I was recovering from
that, I watched a lot of great movies.
One that I really want to recommend is
called The People We Meet on Vacation.
It's on Netflix. I'm not usually a huge
rom-com person, and I feel like it's
been years since a good one has come
out, but this one nailed it. I will say
the main character is a little bit of a
pick-me sometimes, but the story was
really sweet, wholesome, and fun to
watch. I laughed, I cried, I applauded.
Something I'm really looking forward to
is going to Coachella soon. Coachella is
a music festival in the desert in
California,
and it's one of the biggest and most
popular music festivals in the US. I'll
be a first-timer, so I don't really know
what to expect, but I feel like I have a
lot of planning that I need to do. The
festival is 3 days long, and a lot of
people actually camp right on the
festival grounds, but I'll be staying at
a hotel nearby. Justin Bieber is one of
the headliners, and I'm so excited to
see him perform live. Tickets completely
sold out this year, and a lot of people
are saying it's the Bieber effect, and
calling it Biebertella.
There are also a lot of other incredible
artists performing, too. Actually, Big
Bang will be there, too. So, I can't
wait to see them, as well. I know it's
going to be a blast. So, I'll make sure
to vlog while I'm there and make lots of
videos so we can experience it together.
I hope your 2026 has been amazing so
far. The weather is finally starting to
warm up a little bit, and it feels like
a fresh start with the change of
seasons. Stay happy, stay healthy, and
I'll see you next time. Bye.